What do you want to talk about, Klara?
Where do you want to begin?
I don't know.
Okay. If you aren't going
to begin, I will.
Let's see. When was the last time
you left the house? Do you remember?
Well...
August 12th.
Today makes 76 days at home.
Isn't there anything you miss?
I really miss traveling.
The last time I did it,
I went to the beach with my family.
I laughed a lot, actually.
Or with my mother.
The day that it snowed a lot.
Before she died.
But...
But?
But what?
I don't miss how bad I felt
during my last month of school.
How they looked at me,
the people I had thought were my friends.
Or the hours in the hospitals,
the waiting,
the bad news.
I know I'm missing out on a lot
by staying in my house.
But I also feel protected here
from lots of other things.
Right.
I understand.
Feeling safe is very important.
That's how I feel with my family.
How was therapy? Did you tell him
how your new medication is going?
- K2.
- What?
As a psychiatrist, I give you a 7,
but as an annoying sister, a 10.
Okay, whatever.
Hey, isn't it time
for your date with your sweetheart?
- Leave her alone. Don't tease her.
- With your sweetheart?
Even if my sister and her boyfriend
are a little nosy.
- Are you nervous?
- Stop it!
Don't say stuff like that to her.
I hate you both, okay?
So, there is something
that gets you a little bit excited.
There is.
Well, someone I listen to every night.
He's got a sort of radio show.
Hi, everyone.
Thanks for listening
and for being with me here tonight.
This is Follow My Voice,
and I'm Kang, your companion
and your friend for the next hour.
Today's topic is something you've all
asked me about many times: love.
Have you ever been in love?
Did they break your heart?
If so, don't worry.
Time heals all, and you will meet someone
who will make you very happy.
Like I always say...
"We have to learn from the bad,
and turn the page..."
...to move on.
I think a lot about writing to him, but...
I don't know.
I'm sure he gets tons of messages
and he won't even read mine.
You don't know that.
He might answer you.
Do you think so?
Of course.
Alicia asks, "Are you Korean?"
Yes, I was born in Seoul,
but I have been living in Spain
for the past five years.
"When are you going to show your face?"
You already know that embarrasses me.
Someday, I will dare
to reveal my identity.
Today, I asked you guys
about your happiest moments,
and I got a message
that really touched me.
It's a photo of a painting,
a snowy landscape.
I know that place because I went there
with someone very special to me.
Thanks, K. I hope you can
keep on enjoying that place,
even if you miss having
that important someone by your side.
I do.
I don't know
if I'll be able to go back there.
That's why we're here, aren't we?
To keep taking tiny steps every day,
and the first one...
is to try... You say it.
To go out into the world.
FOLLOW MY VOICE
1. GO OUT INTO THE WORLD
Hi
How are you?
Who is this?
Kang
Kang? From Follow My Voice?
Of course hahaha
How many Kangs do you know?
Sorry for bothering
I love the picture you sent me
I noticed it was signed with a K
Did you paint it?
Yes
That's so cool!
But... Hang on! How do I know it's you?
Come on, then, test me.
Okay. Uh...
On tonight's show,
you have to say a code word.
You have to say "cheese."
I miss food.
Well, my friends and family more.
Someday I hope I can go back
and live there again.
Well, that's it for today,
but before the end of Follow My Voice,
I want to tell something about myself.
I totally love cheese.
See you tomorrow.
I'm going to leave you
with a very special song
for a very special person.
Whoever you are,
I can't wait to solve your mystery, K.
Kang.
Do you believe me now
or do I have to do something else?
Well, for now, yeah.
But...
We'll see
if I need anything else from you.
- Come on, honey. We won't make it.
- I'm coming.
- Leaving already?
- Yeah.
Well, if your sister hurries up,
because this hot dog
is going to end up frozen.
Very cute. You're so handsome.
Come on, let's go.
What time will you be back?
Well, uh, 1:30.
- Early, right?
- 2:00?
- 1:30. Yeah.
- 1:30.
You can come too as the mustard.
The three of us can go together.
To a Halloween party
full of 30-somethings?
Uh... How about... no.
Wow.
Okay, then.
I'm asking
in case you don't want to be alone.
No, I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Okay, it's fine.
- Okay.
- Look, it's your loss, okay?
- It's my loss.
- Sure?
- Leave her alone. With 30-somethings...
Call us if you need anything.
- Call us and we'll be here.
- Of course, come on.
- Bye.
- Bye, K.
- I love you.
- Bye. Have fun.
- Come.
- I can't get by if you don't move.
- Okay, I'm going.
- Okay.
I'M NOT GOING TO GET BETTER
I'M NEVER GOING TO LEAVE THE HOUSE
I'M ALONE
I CAN'T BREATHE
IT'S A PANIC ATTACK
- Hello?
I'M GOING TO DIE
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
IT'S KANG
HE'S GOING TO KNOW THAT I'M SICK
-Calm, calm.
- Sorry, I wanted to call my sister.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
No. I can't breathe.
Where are you?
Calm...
I CAN'T BREATHE
I'M NOT OKAY
KANG, PLEASE HELP ME
I'm here. With you.
Okay, we're going to think
about something else.
We're going to think about something nice.
I think it's going to snow next week.
Have you ever watched how the snow falls?
It's as if it's dancing.
Every time a snowflake falls, breathe.
Are you feeling better?
I'm sorry, I have to hang up.
K.
Do you want something to eat?
No.
I just want to sleep.
You've been in bed for days, K.
Do you want...
Do you want us to put on Kang's show?
It's going to start soon.
- No?
- No.
K. Listen.
Even though this happened, I swear,
I swear to you that it's going to be okay.
Everything's going to be okay.
I promise.
- Are you sure?
- Are you looking or not?
Look how far your sister got.
I'm okay!
One! Two!
- Three!
- Yeah!
Mom!
We have to do things now.
We don't know where we'll be tomorrow.
Besides, who knows
when it will snow like this again.
Wow!
I loved it!
- Again?
- Again!
It's terrible. Terrible. It's my fault.
- It's my fault.
- It wasn't your fault.
- Yes. I shouldn't have left her alone.
- This would have happened at any time.
- No, it's my fault.
- It has nothing to do with you.
- It's okay.
- I shouldn't have left her alone.
It's my fault, Andy, it's my fault.
K2.
It's not your fault.
I want to try.
I want to try to go back to school.
I want to try to have a life again...
like before.
Really?
Come on, K. You can do it.
Yeah.
They walked with me for a few blocks and...
then I went the rest of the way alone.
That's great, right?
I'm so pleased. That is excellent news.
I have a map in my room.
And I want to color in
every place I manage to go.
I like it.
In no time at all,
you'll be going off that map. You'll see.
That's it. There it is.
Very good! You've done it. Very good!
I knew you could do it.
So? Nervous about tomorrow?
A little. Yeah.
- A lot.
- It's normal.
We all get nervous
when we go to a new place.
Yeah... Yes.
Klara.
It's just that since I had
those bad days, you know?
I'm afraid that it'll happen again.
No matter what... You know where I am.
- Okay?
- Yeah. Go on.
What if I can't manage
to go to class tomorrow?
Well, if you don't manage tomorrow,
you'll have a chance to go the day after.
And if not that day, then the next.
And if not, then the next.
And that's how you'll build
your daily life bit by bit.
2. BUILD YOUR DAILY LIFE
Hoodie.
Hoodie, new girl, I'm talking to you.
Aren't you going to introduce yourself?
You rather I call you "Hoodie."
And you're mute too.
I'm Klara, with a K.
K-Hoodie with a K.
I'm Diego. Nice to meet you.
Okay.
A truly captivating conversation, huh?
Please, get some
of the soccer team's raffle tickets.
- We need new uniforms.
- Dude, hurry up.
If we keep on like this,
we'll end up playing naked.
Go on, run.
Kang.
Hey.
Who was that on the loudspeaker?
The annoying Kang, yeah.
Good morning, guys. Open your books
to section 3, where we left off yesterday.
- Where is he?
- How's the exam going?
As soon as I get home, I have to study.
Give me your notes. Come on, please.
What do you mean?
- I have to study.
- What about tonight?
Tonight... I want to study.
- I'm a little confused.
- Yeah? Why?
The girl I was talking to
hasn't written me in days.
- Okay, how many days?
- Six.
Dude, just six days.
That's not a big deal.
Actually... nine.
What, what, what? Did I hear that right?
Nine days? Forget her. The message
is loud and clear: not interested.
Diego, shut up already.
You're such a downer.
Okay, but I'm just saying it
so the poor kid can chill out a bit.
Thanks, Diego, but nobody asked you. So...
You're welcome, Kang.
Open!
Hi, Min Seo!
Brother!
Come on, don't get distracted.
You got this wrong.
Dad, we made a mistake!
Let me see.
Well...
your brother had better help you.
Yeah, I'd better.
This isn't your thing either.
When will you guys stop arguing?
We weren't arguing.
It's always the same.
Don't worry about that.
Let's keep drawing...
Hi, folks!
This is Follow My Voice,
and I'm Kang, your companion
and friend for the next hour.
Guys, I've been pretty sad
the last few days.
So I'm going to play a song
that always makes me forget my problems
and gives me the urge to go out again.
I hope you do the same.
- Hi.
- Hi, Yana.
You're not dancing?
Come on, don't be a bore.
Is everything okay?
Everything is... better.
Wanna hit the dance floor?
Uh... Sure, sure.
Kang, I'm sorry for having disappeared.
Well, it's just that I've had
a strange few days.
But anyway... I wanted to say thank you.
Listening to your voice helps me a lot.
Is the "K" for Kandy,
- for Katerina, for Kasilda?
- Don't move.
For... Klara
You guys are so annoying.
How can I paint your portrait
if you're the boy without a face?
I use it so nobody recognizes me
when I sing at a bar downtown.
Well, that's cheating.
It doesn't count if I can't see your face.
Don't laugh, okay? Now you know my secret.
Don't worry, I won't tell anyone...
Batkang.
NEW TALENT
COMPETITION
You're going to think I'm a bit intense,
but you've inspired me,
and I'm writing a new song.
I don't know if it's any good,
but whatever.
There's a competition,
and I want to participate.
Let's see if I can do something cool.
Go for it, Kang.
Maybe I'm moving a little too fast.
I'd love to meet you and I thought
that we could hang out this week.
Any day, if you'd like.
Of course, I'd love to, but this week I...
I don't know if I can. Because I'm away.
Hey, looks like the new girl
has a crush on Kang.
Right? You like Kang?
Typical. He suits you.
No, I don't like him, no, no, no.
Come on, girl, you can tell us.
We're like your best friends, you know?
- Am I right or not, Ellie?
- If you say so.
I'm Perla, and you are?
Klara.
Nice to meet you.
Easy, guys, easy, please, let's go.
Watch out for the broken glass.
Let's go. Come on, this way.
Let's go, quickly.
Come on, out, hurry.
What's up, Hoodie?
- What's up yourself, Diego?
- Nothing, Perla.
I'm not going to stay here, actually.
I'll take a walk around the school.
Wanna come?
What do you say? Ellie?
- I...
- No, I'd better stay here.
We're staying here.
Okay, then. If you change your minds,
you know what to do.
Shout my name, okay?
What's that guy's deal?
- Are you going to meet Klara or not?
- She told me she was away.
- What about you?
- Me?
- Listen--
- You gave it your all.
I have to show off a little.
No, no, no. Don't say my name.
What are you doing? Stop!
- What's wrong with you?
- Nothing's wrong with me. Nothing.
- Why don't you sit next to Yana?
- Nah.
Why not?
Because.
Well, you're an idiot.
Wouldn't it be nice for the two of you
to be out there in the snow,
sharing your body heat?
Kang?
How was your day?
Dude?
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
I just sent a text
and it rang right over there.
- To who, Yana? No, Yana's over there.
- Not to Yana, to Klara.
Stop it!
Klara doesn't give a darn about you!
Look, look.
It's true.
Call her. Call.
Someone's calling you.
No.
Klara, what's wrong?
Nothing.
Klara?
That chick's really weird, man.
I like her.
I can't believe I found you.
Klara?
Can I help you?
Go away.
I don't mind waiting, okay?
Kang, just leave me alone! Go away.
Please.
Okay.
How was your day?
I'm stuck because of the snow
Where can we see each other alone?
- Hi, Kang.
- Hi, Klara.
A chocolate shake.
Candy.
A roll.
This, the chocolate.
I pictured you differently.
How?
Not with this scared face,
you mean? Because...
No, like this.
Your smile...
It's really pretty.
I pictured you differently too.
Yeah, how?
Well, not so, uh...
healthy.
And this boy you've told me about?
Kang is his name, right?
How's it going?
Well, I don't know.
What?
I don't know. You tell me.
Well, he told me he wanted us
to see each other.
And I want to get to know him,
but... I don't know.
I want to, but I'm scared too.
But then I think about it,
and everything that has scared me,
scared me less after I did it.
Just think, Klara, about all the times
that you've been brave.
- Things have always turned out well.
- Yeah, but it's not just seeing him.
I'd like to be honest with him.
I don't know if, when he finds out
certain things about me,
he'll freak out or distance himself or...
Do you like it?
Yeah.
Look.
I made this one.
- This one?
- No, to the left.
- That one?
- That one.
It's the ugliest, isn't it?
Technically,
I've written you a song.
So I think you can paint my portrait now.
Okay.
Well... How would you pose? Let's see.
Like that?
Yeah.
You'll have to stay like that
for a long time.
- Like that?
- Yeah.
I'm comfortable like this.
Uh, okay, great.
Let's see.
No...
I haven't painted in a long time, Kang.
I can't. I'm sorry.
No worries, it's no big deal.
And I didn't tell you
the truth before either.
I haven't this whole time.
I couldn't go to class
because... I was at home.
Because these last few months
have been really hard for me.
I was...
sick, but now I'm better, yeah.
I'm glad.
Come with me, hurry.
I don't know. I think I want to try,
and if it goes well, great.
And if not, well, then I know,
and I stop worrying about it, you know?
Klara, don't worry.
There's no hurry. Don't rush.
But that's how you know.
By being around people
and seeing if you feel good with them
and they feel good with you.
I suppose.
These are addictive, aren't they?
Yeah, a little.
3. DARE TO FEEL
Hoodie!
What did he say?
Nothing, that's for me.
What are you doing, Diego?
Putting a little excitement
in my life, Kang.
You should try it. Look.
- He killed himself.
- Are you okay?
Impressive.
That he's still alive.
What?
What are you all doing here?
That's it, detention for everyone.
Kang, your parents are here.
I'll go with you so I can see
how they give you an earful.
Erick, that's Klara.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
Come on, let's go.
See you around, Klara.
See you around, Kang.
Don't worry about me.
Bye, Diego.
So, just you and me left.
Yeah.
Destiny wants us
to be friends, right, Hoodie?
Why do you call me Hoodie?
I like to be original.
Wow. So original.
Yup.
- You know what?
- What?
Well... I've known your name
for a while now.
How?
I saw you once in the hospital.
In the chemotherapy wing,
when I went to pick up my father.
Yeah, I'm Darío's son.
Who, by the way,
never stopped talking about you.
You always made him laugh.
And he loved it
when you ate all his Jell-O.
I had no idea, Diego.
Yeah, I know.
But we're going to have
to be friends either way.
It will be an honor.
Wait.
- Are you Little Kangaroo?
- No.
- No, no, no.
- I just remembered
- that your father called you that.
- Not me.
- I'm going to call you that from now on.
- No.
- Hoodie!
- Little Kangaroo.
But, K, you got detention.
- I don't understand.
- I know, K2.
- Tell me what happened so I--
- It was cool.
Trust me, I never thought I'd say this,
but I miss school a little bit.
- No, no, no, please, no.
- I'm telling the truth.
- You used to wear certain clothes... No.
- It's true, it's true!
- The pictures we saw...
- I had my own particular style...
- No, no, no.
- You looked horrible, Andy.
Don't change the subject.
What am I going to do with you, K?
Look at me. What should I do with you?
- Should I punish you or what?
- I don't know. Whatever you want...
What? No.
Look,
- you could ground me at home for a week.
- Yeah.
A week more or a week less,
it's all the same.
She's actually right. Isn't she?
I don't know. I just don't know
what to do with you both, honestly.
I missed you. Always stay by my side.
Don't leave me.
Hold me. I love you. Tae-ho.
FACETIME VIDEO
KANG
Hi, Klara.
Hi.
How's it going?
Good. I was just here watching a... Well...
Hey.
What?
Want to meet tomorrow at 11:00?
Well... I don't know if I feel like it.
Kidding, I'm kidding.
Sure, sounds good.
Will you bring me some chocolate?
See you tomorrow.
Okay.
Bye.
Where are you?
I can't see you, Kang.
Follow my voice.
Am I getting there?
I think so.
I found you.
My chocolate.
I forgot it.
Well then, I'm leaving. Goodbye.
No, wait.
I love it.
It was weird
not hearing your show yesterday.
It was impossible because of the snow.
Hey, why don't you ever sing on your show?
Because I'm too embarrassed.
Well, if you enter the competition...
you'll have to sing
in front of a lot of people.
Don't remind me.
If they choose me, will you come with me?
The only thing is,
we'd have to go to Madrid.
Yeah, if you want...
- I can't believe it.
- I messed it up.
I'm going that way.
- Okay...
- Bye.
- Okay, see you later.
- I'm going.
Klara?
Hi.
Can we talk for a minute?
Can we do it later? I'm running late.
Just one minute.
Okay.
Look,
I wanted to ask you something
because... I have some concerns.
Okay, what?
- Is this you?
- Leave me alone, please.
How did you get that?
Where did you find it?
I know Kang really well, and...
And I stood by him during
really, really tough times in his life.
And I know what's good for him
and what isn't.
And someone like you isn't...
I don't think you're good for him.
Wait... I don't understand.
I'm worried about him, you know?
What?
I don't want him to be
with a girl who has so many issues.
Are you guys together? I didn't know.
It doesn't matter
if we're together or not.
He's never going to notice you.
I have friends at your old school
who told me lots of things.
And I don't want to have to send
this video to everyone
to show them who you really are, but...
Have you seen yourself?
Luckily, we did those tests
after your mother's illness.
There's always a genetic risk.
And, in your case, Klara,
the analyses confirm
the presence of cancerous cells.
We have to act as soon as possible.
I'm waiting for you in the car
'Cause it's freezing
It's orange
A little old
I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I had to leave
Another time
Is everything okay?
Klara!
Klara! Hey, Klara!
- Hi.
- I was calling you.
Sorry.
- Wow!
- What?
What a face!
- Thanks.
- No.
- Just what I needed to hear right now.
- No, no, but...
- I didn't mean that.
- Sure.
Don't ask, Diego.
Okay.
Do you want to be alone?
No.
You want to talk about it, right?
Absolutely, yeah.
Well...
I've got an idea.
What?
- Come on.
- I'm coming.
I can't think of a better person
to enjoy this delicacy with.
That's the first nice thing
you've said to me.
Thanks, Hoodie.
I wasn't talking about you.
I was talking about your dad.
Anyway, you're...
ten percent of the reason I'm here.
What? Only ten? No, much more.
- Hey.
- What?
- What do you mean?
- No...
If you keep complaining,
it'll drop to nine pretty soon.
This place is horrible,
and everything that's happened.
But... I like being here with you.
Me too.
Where are you going?
Now you're coming with me.
Okay.
Dad, am I making too much noise?
No, not at all. I like your song.
I think you're going to win.
Kang, I'm here.
If there's anything
you want to talk about, I'm here for you.
Thanks.
Now I understand the K thing.
It feels like a lot of time
has passed, Mommy.
This is my friend. His name's Diego.
So now we're friends, huh?
I wasn't able to come here before.
Forgive me...
for having left you alone
for such a long time.
The other day, I wasn't very clear
when I talked about love.
I didn't say what I was thinking
or what I was actually feeling.
I think that love always makes you suffer.
I'm afraid to fall in love
in case it doesn't work out
and I end up losing that person.
That's what this song is about.
That's why sometimes it's better
not to fight for a love
that's never going to happen
and just accept it as a friendship.
Thank you.
- Look.
- What?
Kang, don't cover yourself.
You're really handsome. Come on.
Kang!
Here.
Wake up, man!
We're going to the party
after this, right?
- No.
- What?
- Come on...
- No, no, no, I only came for that.
Fine, if you're all going,
I'll think about it.
I go to all of them. I never miss one.
- Sure, all of them...
- I go to all...
the ones I'm invited to.
Yeah, and the ones you aren't.
Also.
Kang, shoot!
- Come on!
- Damn!
Wow, great goal.
Kang!
- Come on!
- Bravo!
What are you doing?
Are you taking us to the party?
Not you, no.
Well, me, Perla, Ellie,
and Klara.
I'm not going.
Look, let's do this.
You take us to the party
and I won't tell Klara you spent
the whole game looking at her.
With that little look on your face,
like this.
- Fine.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I said yeah.
Okay.
Girls, get in. Kang's taking us.
By the way, it was a great game.
- No, you in the front. You get car sick.
- Wow. Party! Hello.
What are you talking about?
Party.
- Hi, Kang.
- Start it?
- Hi, K.
- Great game, wasn't it?
Yeah, yeah.
What a piece of junk, man.
Hey, leave him alone.
At least he's taking us.
And I'm in no condition to walk.
What's up, hot stuff? How are you?
- Everything okay? Yeah?
- Good.
Hi. Hello.
Hi.
You actually came.
They talked me into it.
- Awesome.
- Come on, come in.
Those are the ones who talked you into it.
Yeah.
Well, let's go
and then we'll get something to drink.
You played so well in the game.
- Thanks.
- You scored an excellent goal.
What's up?
Who is it?
Nothing. I'll be right back.
Klara, they've chosen me.
- Your song?
- Yeah.
Congratulations, Kang.
I'm really happy for you.
- Can we talk somewhere else?
- Yeah.
I've been a little weird
the last few days.
Well, and you too.
I know.
But I'm always
a little weird anyway, you know?
- That's true.
- Hey!
No, seriously. I'm sorry.
I don't want to ruin our friendship.
I don't want to ruin it either.
Why did you send me that painting?
Because of what you asked for.
It was a place I went to with my mom.
I'm in that painting.
What?
The igloo at the bottom left.
- Yeah.
- I made that.
Well, my brother Jung and I.
What?
Wait, what? You've got a brother?
- Yeah.
- Older than you?
How old is he?
He should have been 21 now,
but he didn't even make it to 19.
That day, the igloo collapsed on top of me
and Jung came to my rescue.
He always did.
One year later, he had an accident
and couldn't play soccer anymore.
That was his dream.
I should have rescued him
like he rescued me.
Jung?
- Jung... committed suicide.
- Jung!
When it was all over,
I blamed the whole world,
but I blamed myself most of all.
It's your fault my brother is dead!
You should have seen him.
I was so sad, so lost,
that I needed the help
of a psychiatrist to go on living.
Thanks to her,
I learned how to control my panic attacks.
I got back everything I had lost.
I managed to go back to school,
and now I'm not looking
at the past every day.
Klara.
I've been looking for you.
Come on, let's talk.
I told you already.
To stay away from Kang.
Now I'm going to have
to tell everyone that you're crazy.
And we'll see
who wants to come near you after that.
There's nothing wrong with me.
- You think so?
- There isn't.
Don't you take pills?
Didn't you spend months
without leaving your house?
Yeah.
Okay. So that's
what I'm going to tell everyone.
I don't care.
- I have nothing to hide.
- No?
Everyone, check what I've sent you.
- This girl, the new girl...
- What is this?
...she left her old school
because she's not right in the head.
Turn it off.
Now everyone is going to see you cry,
because that's what you deserve.
Leave her alone.
Why are you getting involved now?
So you don't do to her
what you do to people.
What you do to me.
Look at this girl.
What are you talking about?
I'm going to tell.
What?
What you did to me.
What you did the other day.
I'm going to tell.
And... who's going to believe you?
- I'm telling too.
- And me.
Me too.
- Hold on--
- I'm also going to tell what you did.
Are you kidding me?
- After everything I've done for you?
- Get out of my house, Yana.
Get out.
- Thanks, guys.
- Thank you.
My first kiss. Kang.
So, tell me,
how have you been feeling these days?
Well...
I don't think
I've felt this way for a long time.
I'm...
happy...
and... I want to feel this happiness...
because I know it won't last forever.
Yeah, you're right.
Forever is a long time.
I'm like this landscape,
which was beautiful
with the snow covering everything.
But... not anymore.
Now the snow is grey
and... soon it will all melt away.
What do you think
your landscape will be like
when the snow disappears
and good weather arrives?
- Come on.
- I don't know.
Hopefully...
like one of those I used to see
when I could travel.
- Full of color and new things.
- Sorry, "hopefully"?
What do you mean, "hopefully"? Girl...
it's going to happen, right?
Whatever it's like,
I'll have to learn to love it.
4. LEARN TO LOVE YOURSELF
- Hi.
Hey, you look so pretty!
I like your curls.
Thanks.
Where are you going?
- What?
- I'm going to the movies.
With whom?
With a friend.
- Aren't you going to ask me anything?
- Um, no.
- No, no.
- Wow.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Okay, then.
Have a good time, K.
- Thanks.
- Okay?
- Bye.
It's this one. Go ahead.
Sorry.
DON'T WORRY...
THINK ABOUT SOMETHING NICE
Mom, yours is much better.
Well, yours will be even better
when you're my age.
How about going for a swim?
- What are you saying?
- No. It's freezing cold. No, no.
How can we come to the beach
and not have a swim? It'd be a shame.
Are you sure?
- Come on.
- Mom, the water will be freezing.
- Aren't you cold?
- Don't think about it!
Come on!
Our clothes! Our clothes!
Come on! Let's go!
It's so cold!
Who did that? Mom! Klara!
No, it's so cold!
So cool, and we almost missed it!
Hey.
What?
You're really pretty.
Hey.
What?
So are you.
Welcome.
Come in.
This is surreal.
What's wrong?
Well...
I just need you to wear
your mask, "Batkang."
Yeah.
Are you going to play a song?
I'm going to tell you something.
Sure.
Um...
Before we met...
I dreamed about you.
Okay. Look.
I closed my eyes,
and you came up close behind me
and hugged me.
- And then...
- Like this?
It was more like... this.
Yeah.
And then I turned around...
and got closer to you.
And what else happened?
Close your eyes.
Close them, but close them for real, okay?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Really.
Okay.
Okay. Now you can open them.
I'm going.
Ow.
Klara,
do you want us
to get the tickets to Madrid?
Sure. Yeah, cool.
Bye, Kang.
No, everything's okay.
Sorry for waking you.
I just couldn't sleep.
So, I just wanted to tell you that...
Kang, I can't go with you to Madrid.
I just don't know if I'm ready for that.
What if I ruin your trip and...
It's a special time for you.
Klara.
You know what it is?
You've fought really hard to get better.
But... I'm not quite there yet.
I need a little more time, Kang.
I have to be okay with myself first.
But... I want you to know
that this doesn't change
the way I feel about you at all.
And I know that love can't conquer all.
It doesn't cure depression or anxiety or...
But it does give me strength
and keeps me going.
That's a lot, Kang.
I hope you understand.
When is Perla leaving?
Perla leaves tomorrow.
- Tomorrow.
- Yeah.
Are you going to miss her?
- Meh.
- Yeah.
- A little.
A little, but we'll see each other soon,
after Christmas.
Yeah.
And do you miss Kang?
By Kang, are you referring
to your secret patient?
- K.
- What?
Well, I couldn't tell you.
No, but, I don't know, you used to...
love listening to his show,
and now you never do.
Yeah.
So?
- "So"? That's it. Shut up.
- That's it. I'm shutting up.
- I won't ask more questions. I promise.
- Okay.
Hi, everyone.
This is Follow My Voice,
and I'm Kang, your companion
and friend during the next hour.
I've never told you that I started
this show at a hard time in my life.
It was part of my therapy.
Talking to you all
made me feel less lonely.
But I kept on hiding.
All that changed
the day you came into my life, Klara.
I want you to know that I understand you
and I'll be thinking of you tomorrow
when I'm on stage.
I WILL HAVE A HAPPY ENDING
- This is so cool!
- Girl!
- No! They're already holding hands.
- What?
No! That's so cute!
Am I going to be surrounded
by couples now?
Well, if Klara's plan
doesn't work out, then no.
- Ha, look how funny that is.
- Just kidding.
Let's go, right?
Uh... Guys, I don't know...
- Come on, come on!
- No, go on!
Hi.
Can you chill out a little?
We're not going to make it.
We are, Hoodie.
As soon as it stops, we'll run, okay?
We'll make it. Relax. Ellie, a joke.
What did one shoe say to another?
How should I know?
Is that your footprint
or is it only my impression?
Come on.
So? Cool, isn't it?
There you are, dude. Don't worry.
There's what? Twenty people?
It's no big deal.
Maybe less, okay?
Come on, man!
That way.
Come on, come on!
Let's go!
Good evening.
I'm Kang,
and tonight is the first time
I've ever performed this song.
It's called "K."
I pictured you differently
But I like you better this way
With highlights in your hair
And eyes the color of the sea
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Sorry. Excuse me.
The summers will pass
We'll grow older
You'll meet some guy
He'll write you better songs
And someday, I
Will be a beautiful memory
And all that will remain of this love
Is a whisper in your ear
If your heart races
And you look strange in the mirror
Even if you can't see anything
Follow my voice
There is no darkness
That can't be made light
Before, I thought a lot about
everything I was missing out on.
But, actually,
what I missed the most was myself.
And now that I've spent
76 days out of my room,
everything is different.
Thanks to the best family in the world
for reminding me who I am.
You guys encouraged me
to go to therapy, and...
and thanks to that, now I can see...
what kind of landscape I am
and what kind I can be.
And thanks to the people
who came into my life
when I wasn't letting
anyone be a part of it.
And to your voice.
For always inspiring me
and... helping me
to find the strength to be myself again.
These paintings show how my life
has filled with color.
How I found my own voice and...
and decided to follow it.
5. FOLLOW YOUR VOICE
5. FOLLOW MY VOICE